# JOSHUA, JOSHUA CHIZARAM

7 PREFAB CLOSE GRA PHASE III

#### PORT HARCOURT

#### RIVERS STATE.

+234 (0) 8134158968

joshuajosh59@gmail.com

#### PERSONAL INFORMATION

DATE OF BIRTH: 09<sup>TH</sup> MARCH, 1993

SEX: MALE
MARITAL STATUS: SINGLE
STATE OF ORIGIN: ABIA

LOCAL GOVERNMENT OF ORIGIN: UMUAHIA SOUTH.

NATIONALITY: NIGERIA

RELIGION: CHRISTIANITY

## **CAREER OBJECTIVE**

To use my educational background, Experience, Skill and genuine enthusiasm to assist an organization or individual that recognizes Competence and Hard work to providing Quality services and to be committed to a Functional career development.

#### PERSONAL ATTRIBUTE:

Honesty, Hard work, team player with a drive to succeed. Can cope well under pressure, committed to organizational goal and objective. Natural leader and has lots of acquired skills.

# **HOBBIES:**

Traveling, Playing Games, Reading, Surfing the Net and listening to music.

# **EDUCATION:**

YEAR	QUALIFICATION	INSTITUTION

2013- 2017 Bachelor of Computer Science University of Port Harcourt (B.comp Sci) Rivers State.

2014 Digital Business Management Lagos Business School (**Digital Business Manager**) Pan-Atlantic University.

2004-2010	SSCE/OL	Adventist Technical Secondary School,
		Abia State
2001-2004	FSLC	Margretwell Nursery School, Ashaka,

## **WORK EXPERIENCE**

## MICROSOFT INC

MICROSOFT STUDENT PARTNER JANUARY 2016 – PRESENT

## **DUTIES**

Run workshops and hackathons

Host tech events and give demos on campus

Work alongside Microsoft professionals, assisting them during hackathons and events Join exclusive Microsoft training events to learn the latest technologies Grow and nurture a community of students and faculty on-campus and online

# ABIA STATE GOVERMENT Digital Analyst SEPTEMBER 2015 –

#### **DUTIES**

Maintain the Government Website
Promote the Government Online
Digital Marketing Analysis
Help Government receive better feedback medium from the people.

## **GOOGLE INC**

GOOGLE STUDENT AMBASSADOR JUNE 2014 – JULY 2015

## **DUTIES**

- Campus contact for Google Team
- Update School on Google Products and Programs
- Plan and host events on Campus
- Help Google better understand University's culture

# **AVONDALE SERVICES & SUPPLIES LIMITED**

IT PERSONELL / OPERATIONS ASSISTANT. MAY 2012 -NOVEMBER 2014

# **DUTIES**

Develop their Official Website,
Manage the company Mail,
Monitor and maintain the Computer System,
Configure and install Computer System,
Diagnose Software and Hardware faults,
Solve technical issues either over the phones or in person.

## ETI HEALTH & LEISURE LIMITED

IT PERSONELL. SEPTEMBER 2011 – APRIL 2012

## RESPONSIBILITIES AND ACHIEVEMENTS

#### PRACTICES / SKILLS/ CERTIFICATES

ONLINE MARKETING LAB ALUMNI
GOOGLE ADWORDS CERTIFIED
CCNA (CISCO COMPUTER NETWORKING ASSOCIATE)
WEB DEVELOPMENT
JAVA SCRIPT0
C++
C#

# LIST OF PUBLICATIONS:

## **REFEREES:**

Dr. Ayibatonye Owei

Commissioner for Health, Bayelsa State. otansi@yahoo.com

## Cynthia Ibisiki.

Operations Manager Avondale Services & Supplies Ltd eoyiwe@yahoo.com

## Jeminatu Alabi-isama

Out-Reach Education Manager, Sub-Sahara Africa Google Inc. Jeminatua@google.com